[
    {
        "question": "How much do you think I love you?",
        "answer-1": "Only a little",
        "answer-2": "Could be more",
        "answer-3": "Idk",
        "answer-4": "A WHOLE LOTTT",
        "right_answer": "A WHOLE LOTTT"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is better than you?",
        "answer-1": "No one",
        "answer-2": "Joe Mama",
        "answer-3": "Gerard Butler",
        "answer-4": "Optimus Prime",
        "right_answer": "No one"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is my favorite nickname you call me?",
        "answer-1": "Coolest Loser",
        "answer-2": "Babe",
        "answer-3": "Manu",
        "answer-4": "Fatty",
        "right_answer": "Coolest Loser"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do I love about you?",
        "answer-1": "The way you smile",
        "answer-2": "The way you laugh",
        "answer-3": "The way you look",
        "answer-4": "All of the above",
        "right_answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do I love about you Part 2?",
        "answer-1": "You're the smartest person I know",
        "answer-2": "You're the hottest person I know",
        "answer-3": "You're the funniest person I know",
        "answer-4": "Silly me, it's all of the above",
        "right_answer": "Silly me, it's all of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do I love about you Part 3?",
        "answer-1": "Your style",
        "answer-2": "Your dedication",
        "answer-3": "Your burps",
        "answer-4": "Would you look at that, it's all of the above",
        "right_answer": "Would you look at that, it's all of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the setence, I was walking down the street and _________?",
        "answer-1": "I fell",
        "answer-2": "I kept walking",
        "answer-3": "I found a dollar",
        "answer-4": "LAPOTAPOTAPOT",
        "right_answer": "LAPOTAPOTAPOT"
    },
    {
        "question": "If we ever played overcooked again, would we win?",
        "answer-1": "We'd be cooked",
        "answer-2": "Hell yeah we would",
        "answer-3": "Nah",
        "answer-4": "I don't think so",
        "right_answer": "Hell yeah we would"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the most perfect girl in the world?",
        "answer-1": "Not writing another female's name",
        "answer-2": "Easy, you",
        "answer-3": "I'm not falling for the trap",
        "answer-4": "You're the only girl on my mind fr",
        "right_answer": "Easy, you"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times will I tell you I love you?",
        "answer-1": "Never",
        "answer-2": "Every single day till the day I die",
        "answer-3": "Once a day",
        "answer-4": "Eh sometimes",
        "right_answer": "Every single day till the day I die"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who do I want as my Valentine every year?",
        "answer-1": "You, silly",
        "answer-2": "Goku",
        "answer-3": "Optimus Prime",
        "answer-4": "No one",
        "right_answer": "You, silly"
    }
]
